https://www.daycarehotline.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - How to Start a Daycare | Start a Home Daycare | Daycare Forms
About UsContact UsReviews and TestimonialsHow to Start a DaycareRSS FeedContact UsFollow Us On TwitterFollow Us On FacebookFollow Us On Google+Follow Us On LinkedInFollow Our Channel On YouTube
Email Us: support@childcare-marketing.com
HomeDaycare ProductsHow to Start a DaycareDaycare FormsDaycare Policy HandbookDaycare GrantsDaycare Center Business Plan TemplateHome-Based Daycare Business PlanKris MurrayBlogHow to Start a DaycareChild Care Marketing News and ArticlesDaycare BusinessChild Care EducationFinding a DaycareFrequently Asked QuestionsState Daycare License RequirementsFind a Daycare
Privacy Policy TweetTweetPrivacy Policy The information obtained from those visiting our website is used as follows: Security : All data collected on our secure product order forms will be encrypted for your security and privacy. Your personal information is used for processing and shipping purposes only. This allows us to confirm your payment information and protect you from fraud.Information Collected: Our website does not
use cookies to obtain information about you. Unless you place an order with our company we do not have any records pertaining to your visit with the exception of the search engine used to find our site which allows us to track the number of visits to our site. Those placing an order have provided information pertaining to their name, address, phone, email, IP address and credit card information, this information will not be passed onto any third parties except the credit card processing agency we use to authorize your credit card charge.No Spam:
Daycare Hotline maintains a strict “no-spam” policy. Your e-mail address or mailing address will not be sold or rented to a third party. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that the Daycare Hotline does not own or control, or to people that the Daycare Hotline does not employ or manage.Disclosure and Transfer: The Daycare Hotline does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested. It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law. Those consumers who purchase products from this site have provided us with name, address, phone, email, IP address and credit card information, in the event that the Daycare Hotline is sold or merged with another company, we will transfer information about you regarding your name, address, phone number, email address and the item you ordered. We will not disclose credit card information under any circumstances.Links to other Websites:
Our Website may contain links to Websites that are provided and maintained exclusively by third parties Websites provided and maintained by third parties are not subject to this privacy policy. Please review the privacy policies on those Websites to understand their personal information handling practices. We make no representations concerning the privacy policies of these third party Websites.Changes to this Policy:
Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes. Although we reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy, we will provide notice to you on this Web site of any major changes for at least 30 days following the change.Privacy Policy modified 05/05/2014
Contact UsAbout UsPrivacy PolicyDisclaimerAffiliate Partner ProgramHow to White ListHow to Start a DaycareCopyright © 2014 Daycare Systems LLCRSS FeedContact UsFollow Us On TwitterFollow Us On FacebookFollow Us On Google+Follow Us On LinkedInFollow Our Channel On YouTube
